[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2005 movie stars Johnny Knoxville, Jessica Simpson and a muscular Dodge Charger.", "correct_answer": "The Dukes of Hazzard", "incorrect_answers": ["Desert Motel", "Lord of War", "Transporter 2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mix 1 ts powdered sugar and 2 ts water with some crushed ice into a glass. Then add 2 1/2 oz bourbon whiskey and some mint sprigs on top. \nYou should leave it until the glass is frosted.", "correct_answer": "Mint Julep", "incorrect_answers": ["Margarita", "Pina Colada", "Froot Loop"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The World No Tobacco Day, a global event sponsored by the World Health Organization, is held annually on which day?", "correct_answer": "May 31", "incorrect_answers": ["March 31", "April 31", "January 1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is credited for the initial idea of the Back to the Future movies?", "correct_answer": "Bob Gale", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael J Fox", "Steven Speilberg", "Robert Zemeckis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the animals listed below has the longest gestation period?", "correct_answer": "Elephant", "incorrect_answers": ["Rhinoceros", "Tiger", "Boar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which planet of the Solar System has been nicknamed The Red Planet?", "correct_answer": "Mars", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury", "Neptune", "Venus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happened to the tropical coral reefs during the 1998 and 2004 El Nino weather phenomenons?", "correct_answer": "Many of them were bleached or even killed", "incorrect_answers": ["Some of them exploded", "They all thrived", "Nothing as they were all deep underwater"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the The Rio Grande river called in Mexico?", "correct_answer": "Rio Bravo", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Rio Rojo", "Rio del Fuego"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1877 American astronomer Asaph Hall discovered the two moons of Mars. Who was the first writer to mention these moons?", "correct_answer": "Jonathan Swift", "incorrect_answers": ["Issac Asimov", "Mark Twain", "Benjamin Franklin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tornadoes are transparent at first until dust and debris are picked up.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This sign is positioned between the horse and the dragon.   In ancient China it was associated with wisdom and aesthetic beauty.", "correct_answer": "Snake", "incorrect_answers": ["Rabbit", "Rat", "Rooster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which hobby would you need frames, hoops and canvas?", "correct_answer": "Needlepoint", "incorrect_answers": ["Nudism", "Newsletter printing", "Netball"]}]